





Total Experience: 4 Year(s) 0 Month(s) Current Designation: System Engineer

Current Company: Tata Consultancy Services Ltd. Notice Period: 2 Months Current Location: Kolkata **Highest Degree:**

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Kolkata, Pune Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Tech Support Enanr

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: System/Tech Support Engineer, Application Support, Production Support, Design Development, Project

 ${\bf Management, Software\ Engineering, Information\ Security, Data}$

Structures, Troubleshooting, Installation, Debugging, MATLAB, Python, HTML, CSS, AWS, C, C++

Verified : Le Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Summary

Experience of more than 3.5 years in "Development", "Testing", "Application Support", "Production Support ", "Debugging", Analysis & Issue Resolving, "Enhancement",

Hands-on Experience in SQL/PLSQL Developer, Unix/Linux platform, ETL tools, BI, Oracle Forms

Handling the installation, maintenance, support, troubleshooting of Oracle Retail Enterprise Suite

Business and functional knowledge in Oracle RMS, REIM, WMS, RPM, RESA

Basic Knowledge in Python, Microservices, AWS

Self-motivated, flexible, quick learner, hardworking personality, team-player with excellent team-building skills.

Adroit in giving best effort to meet deadline given by Customers.

Adroit in providing effective resolution to customer queries related to project.

Work Experience

Tata Consultancy Services Ltd. as System Engineer

Dec 2016 to Till Date

Client Name Morrisons Supermarket PLC Project Title Transition & Production Support

May 2017 to April 2019 Period Position

Support Analyst

Support Analyst
ties * Contributed in Automation and Key System Improvement Processes for Business on client's Responsibilities request.

- On-Call Support Person for Support to critical situations and emergencies.
- Offshore Team member for the Retail Operations (RMS/RIB/RPMRESA/ReIM)
- Have good experience in SLA management, Reporting, system health checks and Trouble Shooting, Integration
- Was part of TCS Project Team during multiple transition & migration for in-house Production support.
- Actively involved in Enhancement, Testing, Documentation process

Platforms/OS Unix, Linux, Windows 7, Windows 10

Software/Technology Pro*C, PL/SQL (Oracle 11g Database), Oracle Front End Applications, Oracle BI Project Location TCS- Kolkata, India

Client Name Morrisons Supermarket PLC

Project Title DevOps May 2019 to Present Period

Technology Analyst Position

Responsibilities Contributed in Design Review & Code Review for multiple System Improvement Planning

- Lead Role in multiple Cutover & Outage Activities
- Manual Testing & Signoff for Major Projects
- Contributed in Al- ML Project (Machine First Delivery Model) to eliminate human intervention from daily BAU processes.

Platforms/OS Unix, Linux, Windows 7, Windows 10
Software/Technology PL/SOL (Oracle 11g Database) Oracle Front End Applications Oracle Forms

Important

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Project Location TCS- Kolkata, India

^ Back to Top

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electrical) from Maulana Abul kalam Azad university of Technology in 2016

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs: Certification Course

^ Back to Top

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
MS OFFICE	365	2021	15 Year(s) 1 Month(s)
Oracle Retail Merchandising System	13	2021	4 Year(s) 1 Month(s)
WINDOWS OS	10	2021	15 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
ORACLE FORMS	10	2021	1 Year(s) 1 Month(s)
Oracle BI		0	2 Year(s) 1 Month(s)
Invoice Processing		0	3 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
AWS		0	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
PLSQL		0	4 Year(s) 1 Month(s)
Unix/Linux	Redhat	2021	4 Year(s) 1 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Bengali				

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Physically Challenged: No

Work Authorization

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQs - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.